Hello! This time I'm joined by Ruru Dambara from Juice Juice and
and Kisora Niinuma from Tsubaki Factory.
As usual on Hello! STE is a program that gives you the latest information about Hello! Project.
This time we're going to show you the latest news of Hello! Project
This time it's a special edition!
This time, we'll be presenting the Hello Project 25th Anniversary New Member Audition Announcement Special!
We'll be announcing the members who have passed the audition.
The successful audition winners are
We are happy to announce that the successful audition winner will be joining Tsubaki Factory!
Thank you very much for coming to our studio for the final audition, where we made a surprise announcement.
I, Kisora Niinuma, will graduate from Tsubaki Factory and Hello Project after this year's spring tour.
I was very happy to be able to announce the acceptance of such a member who will lead Tsubaki Factory after my graduation.
Now, I would like to announce to the current members of Tsubaki Factory that a new member has joined the group.
and the surprise acceptance announcement to the new members.
Please take a look.
We're not here to film Iruze Tsubaki Factory, but to make an important announcement.
Oh, my God!
A new member will join Tsubaki Factory!
The new members are the successful candidates of Hello Project's 25th anniversary audition, and they're here for the final audition.
We'd like to inform them that they're going to join Tsubaki Factory.
I hope you're all ready for that, so here we go! I'm so excited!
Let's make the announcement!
Excuse me, good afternoon.
First of all, I'd like to ask you to come to the camera here.
Please look at the camera and tell us your grade, age, hometown, and name. I'm 13 years old, in the second year of junior high school, from Osaka.
I look forward to working with you.
Today is the final round.
Please tell us about your enthusiasm and determination for the audition.
I've worked hard and practiced a lot, so I have no regrets.
I want to work even harder in the future.
Ms. Doi, do you want to be a member of Hello Project?
Yes, I do.
Ms. Doi passed the Hello Project 25th anniversary new member audition!
Congratulations! Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yay, yay, yay.
Wow!
I want to keep crying.
How are you feeling now, Yari?
I'm happy. I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
Let's do our best together.
Let's do our best.
Thank you very much.
Yay. Congratulations. Here you go.
Ahh!
So, yes, a new member.
The other one is on the way.
me
Me...
No. 2, hello in Spain!
No.1, Michi
I'm 13 years old, in the second year of junior high school, and I'm Yu Murata, from Aichi Prefecture.
Today is the final round, Yu Murata, please tell us about your enthusiasm and determination for the audition.
I want to make sure that I won't regret my decision because I've made it to the final round.
I want to do my best so that I can give a good report to the people who have helped me.
Yu Murata, do you want to be a member of Hello Project?
Yes, I do.
Yu Murata, you have passed the Hello Project 25th anniversary new member audition!
Yay! Congratulations!
And now you are going to join Tsubaki Factory!
Yay! Congratulations! You have joined the league!
So, how do you feel about your height now?
I'm so happy that I finally made it!
It's great!
Let's work hard together!
Please, please, please, please, please.
Please, please, please, please.
And one more.
There's one more.
We have a successful candidate.
Thank you very much for watching, please state your grade, age, hometown, and name for the camera. I am Miu Ishii, a 15-year-old junior high school student from Kanagawa Prefecture.
Today is the final screening. Miu Ishii, please tell us about your enthusiasm and determination for the audition.
I loved Hello Project very much, so I was very happy to be accepted from the third round, but for the next round
I have been practicing hard for the next audition.
Yes, I did.
I have worked very hard.
Miu Ishii.
Do you want to be a member of Hello Project?
Would you like to be a member of Hello Project?
I would like to be a member of Hello Project.
Miu Ishii
Halo Project 25th Anniversary
New member audition
She passed.
Congratulations!
And she's going to join Tsubaki Factory.
to join Tsubaki Factory.
Congratulations!
How do you feel now?
I don't know what the dreamy reality is anymore.
Let's work hard together from now on.
Best regards.
Ahhhhhh...
So, we have three new members.
Two of them
There they are!
I see, Mr. Mura, so the three of you didn't know that each other had been accepted.
Oh, I see.
Congratulations!
me
So, all 12 members of the new Tsubaki Factory are here!
From now on, we senior members would like to ask questions to the new members as much as we can, so if you have any questions, what should we call you?
I've been told that I'm usually called Hane, but I don't have a heart for Minami, or Miha, or Miha, or Miha-chan, or Miha-chan, or Miha-chan, or Miha-chan, or Miha-chan...
Mihachan or Mihachan...
Mihachan.
I don't have a nickname either.
I just call her Yu-chan or Yuu.
Like extending it.
I see.
My friends usually remember me as Fu-chan.
I'm not Chuchan, I'm Keshi, but I'm going to start making calls at the camp, so I guess so.
And it's important, isn't it? I like you guys at Tsubaki Patry. I know! I knew it!
I'm glad you know. I'm so happy.
I've got a lot of parts open right now.
I want to do Alfreenam, which is just my fantasy that I practiced during the audition.
It was an audition song.
It was an audition.
It was an audition song. I want to do the only fantasy afreenam I've practiced in the audition.
It was my audition song.
I don't do mistakes, I don't do mistakes, but it's my favorite song, and I want to perform that.
I was wondering if you have any special skills.
I was wondering if you have any special skills or hobbies, hobbies, air, or dance that you're looking forward to.
Aaaaah!
I'm not really good at ballet, but if it's not that genre, I can do my best.
I can do it!
That's good!
Good, good, good.
What about you, Yoo-chan?
I'm a dancer too.
I've been doing it for about five years, but I'm not much of a guest dancer.
I like jazz dance and that adult-ish stuff, like k-pop.
Me Watcher
My apprentice is good at Go and Soran Star!
me
Oh, no! Igo-chan does the Soran! Yes!
I also do the soran with Igo!
Tsubaki, look, you're dancing.
Soran! I'm doing the soran!
Oh, you're going that way.
Oh, I made a mistake. Where shall we go?
Where shall we go?
Let's dance together!
So, is there anyone in your senior class that you admire?
I really love you all.
Masaki Sato and...
The big ballet!
Dai Bal.
and Sakura Ishiyama, Mao Akiyama and Maolin Fukuda.
You do it, too, Marin!
I'm so sorry I missed it!
Okay, Yu-chan, I'm Rikaku Sasaki from Angeleum!
Buber, your dance is powerful and yes, I was asked. Yes, I was asked. Please go ahead.
Yes, I'm Rikaku Sasaki from Angeleum. Female Mercury.
Yes... I've never been asked before, but here I am!
So, the 12 of us are going to work as Tsubaki Factory again as a new organization.
I hope to make many dreams come true with you all, so please continue to support us.
When I say that's all I have to say, please say with me that it was Tsubaki Factory.
Please do so.
That's all for now, this is Tsubaki Factory.
So, three members, Miu Ishii, Yu Murata, and Fuka Doi, have decided to join Zubaki Factory!
Congratulations!
The video was a very happy announcement of the three new members.
I would be happy if you could give me your first impressions of the three new members.
First of all, the first one to join the group, Fuka Yunfuka, really looked like a puppy.
The three of them came to Perth for the final screening, so I think they were probably very nervous.
So it was quite unexpected that the Utsubaki members were there.
I think they were surprised at first.
I asked him if he wanted to join Hello! Project, I asked him if he wanted to be a member of Hello!
Project, she answered with a very sincere and sincere expression, and she tried her best to express her feelings.
I got the impression that she was very fresh and excited about the future.
When I asked her about her special skill, she answered "dancing.
So she is a dancer.
What kind of dance will you show us?
She's pretty clear.
I mean, she's very clear.
I'm sure you're a good MC.
I'm sure.
I'm sure you'll say "a lot".
I'm personally looking forward to seeing her work in various aspects.
And the last three birds are really adorable.
I was also impressed by her eyes, and when I asked her about her love for Hello Project, she answered "I really like Hello Project".
And when I asked her what her favorite song was in Matsumaki, she answered "Kyokyuu Story" (the best story).
I was very happy to hear that she knew ATSUBAKI because I don't think there are many girls who know that much about the album's songs.
I was very happy to hear that.
I thought that this is a member who will carefully pass on the love for Tsubaki to the next generation.
That's what I'm looking forward to.
I hope you will become a member from now on.
I'm looking forward to seeing Miharu singing her favorite songs as a member again.
I'm looking forward to seeing Miharu singing my favorite songs as a member again.
The way she was talking so hard with tears in her eyes was really cute.
It's really cute and I can feel she's really happy, but she also looks like she's nervous.
But you could also tell that she was so nervous that she didn't know what to do.
I could really feel it.
I thought the video was like a new member announcement.
Haloste
We've announced the successful candidates of Hello Project's 25th anniversary audition so far.
I've announced the successful candidates of the auditions for Hello Project's 25th anniversary.
From among the audition participants
to make their debut in Hello Project.
Hello Project trainees to make their debut in the Hello Project.
Please take a look at the introduction video.
Here she is, a 15-year-old junior high school student from Kanagawa Prefecture, Shimokawa Hana.
I'm Hana Shimokawa, a 15-year-old junior high school student from Kanagawa Prefecture.
My special skills are theater and hula dancing.
Masumi, are you okay with ink?
Yeah. Sumi. Birthdays are not just for saying happy birthday.
It's not just a day to say happy birthday.
It's also a day to say thank you.
I found an environment where I can learn the music I love for the first time, so I will do my best to improve as much as I can. I look forward to working with you.
I joined the Halo Pro trainees. I am 14 years old, in the second year of junior high school, and I am Yurika Asano from Kanagawa Prefecture.
My special skill and hobby is chair dancing.
I am good at dancing, so I would like to practice a lot so that I can give a good performance in front of everyone. I look forward to working with you.
I joined the Halo Pro trainees. I am Chihiro Miyakoshi, a 13-year-old first-year junior high school student from Tokyo.
My hobby is dancing, and I am also good at it.
My singing is still in its infancy, but I would like to make the most of my dancing skills and do my best. Please do me a favor.
I joined the Halo Pro trainees.
I am 13 years old, a first-year junior high school student from Kanagawa, Japan.
My hobby is going to Halo Pro live. Fate's Journey: Beauty Troupe, Let's make coincidences bloom, let's call forth miracles.
I have no experience in singing or dancing, but I will do my best to give a unique performance.
I joined the Halo Pro trainees.
I'm Yumi Soma, a 12-year-old middle school student from Saitama Prefecture.
My hobbies and skills are singing and dancing.
I am good at singing and dancing, so I will do my best to make the best use of them so that everyone will cheer for me.
I'm 12 years old and a sixth grader from Kanagawa prefecture.
My hobbies are fashion and my special skill is cheerleading. I'm Mano Otsubo, a 12-year-old sixth grader from Kanagawa Prefecture.
My hobby is to dress up and my specialty is cheerleading. As a Halo Pro trainee, there are still many things I don't know about.
I'm going to take advantage of my chair dance to showcase my special dance skills, and
I am also going to try singing for the first time.
I would like to challenge many things as a Halo Pro trainee.
I would like to challenge a lot of things as a trainee member of Halo Pro.
I have joined the Halo Pro trainee program. I am Hikari Yoshida, a 12-year-old sixth grader from Tokyo.
My special skill is to make everyone smile. My hobbies are writing calligraphy and ballet. Halo Project has a lot of good songs and great songs, so I will do my best to give a good performance of them.
I look forward to working with you.
I am a trainee member of Halo Project. I am 12 years old and in the 6th grade of elementary school.
My hobbies are making candy fruits and dancing. My special skill is dancing. We are all of one mind, one heart, one brave soul.
I have been good at dancing since I was a child, but I am not so good at singing.
I am good at dancing, but I am not so good at singing.
I would like to improve my singing skills.
I would like to improve that a lot.
I'm a trainee of Halo Pro.
I am 10 years old and in the 5th grade from Aichi prefecture.
My hobby is to do idol dances with my sister.
My special skill is acrobatics.
There are many things I am not good at, but I will do my best to keep up with you all!
I look forward to working with you!
We are happy to announce that 9 new trainees have joined HadPro!
Thank you very much!
They are all young!
My first impression is that they are young.
There are many junior high school and elementary school students.
I also joined the group as a trainee.
We're all the same age.
It was about 10 years ago.
How old were you?
I was in sixth grade.
I was 14 or something.
I think I was in eighth grade.
I was about that age.
That's really how old they were.
suddenly joined the group.
I was in training for about four years.
I was a trainee for about four years.
I was in the sixth grade, so I didn't have any experience as a senior.
I learned the rules of various organizations for the first time.
I am really glad to have been a trainee.
I'm really glad that I was a trainee.
I'm really glad that I was a trainee because it's very important at the beginning, and I'm really glad that I was a trainee.
It's very important at the beginning, so I want you all to listen to various people and absorb things in various ways.
I want you to listen to all kinds of people, absorb all kinds of things, and grow up.
We are also members who debuted after having experienced the Halo Pro trainee period.
I want you all to do your best and make your debut.
I hope you all do your best and make your debut.
I thought there were a lot of girls who were good at dancing this time.
I had the impression that many of them were good at dancing.
There were some who are actually good at theater and some who are doing contemporary dance.
I got the impression that there were more students with special skills that we have never seen before.
It was a lot of fun.
I mean, it made me smile.
It was like watching us in the past.
We have 9 new members who I am really looking forward to seeing in the future.
I would like to ask everyone to please support the nine members as they aim for their new debut with Hello Project.
Hello! Ste!
So, I'd like to introduce the three new members of Tsubaki Factory and the nine new members of
and the 9 new members who will join the Halo Pro trainees.
It's so exciting to see our dreams come true
I can feel everyone's excitement, and it makes my heart pound.
Here is Kisora to the new members of Tsubaki Factory.
I would like to announce what I expect from the new members of Halo Pro trainees.
I've written them in my sketchbook, so I'd like to share them with you.
Let's do it!
Ta-da!
Let's start with Kisora.
Yes, I'm a character!
Tsubaki Factory is a group full of unique members, so I'm looking forward to seeing what kind of characters these three will be.
I'm looking forward to seeing what kind of characters the three of them will fight with, and I'm also looking forward to seeing how the atmosphere of the group will change with the addition of the three of them.
I'm really looking forward to that as well, so that's why I chose them as characters.
It's true that I couldn't say that much about my personal side at the stage of the announcement, so I decided to make them characters.
So, what I expect from the new members of the Halo Pro trainees is smiles and power.
I'm looking forward to seeing the smiles and power of the new members of the trainees.
I hope that they will bring smiles to everyone's faces with their smiles and power. I have high expectations for them. I hope the three new members of Tsubaki Factory will do their best in the future,
I hope the three new members of Tsubaki Factory will do their best in the future, and I also hope the new members of the Halo Pro trainees will do their best to make their debut.
I hope the new members of Tsubaki Factory will do their best in the future. Ste!
I'm 15 years old and a junior high school student from Kanagawa Prefecture.
I joined Tsubaki Factory, and there are many songs that I like,
I'm going to practice and do my best so that I can sing them well.
I look forward to your continued support.
I am Yu Murata, a 13-year-old junior high school student from Aichi Prefecture.
I'm going to do a lot of live performances from now on.
I would like to interact with my fans and bring smiles to their faces.
I want this year to be a year of sparkling and shining, so I will work harder and harder from now on.
I am 13 years old, a junior high school student from Osaka, Japan.
I will do my best as a member of Tsubaki Factory, so please take care of me.
I will do my best as a member of Tsubaki Factory. sta. of JuiceJuice
Ruru Tamba of JuiceJuice,
JuiceJuice's Ayaruru Tamba and Tsubaki Factory's Kisara Niinuma will be presenting "Halo! STE.
It's time to say goodbye.
This time, we'll be talking about the audition for new members to celebrate the 25th anniversary of the Halo! Project 25th Anniversary New Member Audition Announcement Special.
Project 25th Anniversary New Member Audition Announcement Special.
The sparkling and happy faces of the new members really filled the screen.
I think it was a very wonderful special meeting.
I am very happy that three new members have joined Tsubaki Factory this time.
I'm really looking forward to seeing Tsubaki in the future.
I myself will be graduating soon, so the time I can spend with the new members will be a little short.
I hope I can teach them what I can do now and make a wonderful group.
The new members of Tsubaki Factory will be performing at the "Hello Project 2024 Winter 3 of 3" event at Tachikawa Stage Garden on February 10th.
Hello Project 2024 Winter 3 of As
Team A will be performing at the Tachikawa Stage Garden on February 10.
And, as you know, Team A will be performing in Aichi on February 17.
February 18 in Hyogo and February 23 in Hokkaido.
I'll be greeting the audience!
That's great!
For the three of us...
February 10 will be their first time on stage.
I'm sure they will be very nervous.
But I think that nervousness is something you can only experience on that day.
I'll probably be there for them all the time, so I'll try to ease their nerves and make it a great unveiling.
I'll be broadcasting the audition for the three of you on February 8 on UPCAMINITY, and since it will be the first time for me and I'm sure for all of you to see the audition, I'd like to know how you're going to sing and dance.
It will be the first time for me and all of you to see how they sing and dance.
It will be the first time for me to see the auditions, so I'm sure everyone will be looking forward to it.
Let's all pay attention!
The new members of the Halo Pro trainees introduced this time are
The presentation of the Hello Project trainees will be held on March 2.
Hello Project Trainee Presentation 2024
They will perform at the March Mimoza
The new trainee members are also
They were all very sparkling, so let's go and support them!
Let's all go and cheer them on!
Let's watch over them!
Haloste is a channel where the members of Halo Project will appear more and more. New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!
This time, our partners in Haloste are Danbaralulu from JuiceJ and Rinnumaki Sora from Tsubaki Factory.
bye bye